I'm so happy right now, because you all are with me.
現在有大家陪伴，我真的很開心
Let's be friends forever.
我們要當一輩子的朋友喔
Kanade. I love you.
小奏，我喜歡你
I'm never letting you go.
-我不會放開你的 -我也是
Kanade's dad didn't commit suicide.
小奏的爸爸當年不是自殺
He was murdered.
是被殺死的
What?
什麼？
Kanade's dad was--
-小奏的爸爸… -別說了！
Why did Kaori…
為什麼香織會…
Depending on what you say, my son might need a lawyer.
畢竟若有必要 我可能得幫兒子找位律師
Masaki, wait! Don't go!
真樹，等一下！你不要走
I'm the one who…
是我把香織…
Someone who I thought loved me disappeared from in front of me again.
原以為愛著自己的對象 又從我面前消失了
The patient is male in his twenties or thirties.
推測這名男性患者為20幾歲或30幾歲 身分目前不明
-There's something I want to tell you. -What?
-我有事想跟你談談 -什麼事？
I must go somewhere…
我有地方要去
Kanade Nishimura, how many years have you been a prosecutor?
西村奏，你當檢察官幾年了？
Sorry?
什麼？
How long have you been doing this?
我是在問你的年資
Six years and three months.
六年三個月
You've been a prosecutor for six and a half years.
資歷六年半的檢察官
Do you truly think a deposition from an accomplice
真的認為只憑共犯的證詞
is sufficient to go to trial?
就能在法庭起訴嗎？
I was prosecuting a case
我所負責的案件是
involving illegal drug deals that occurred a week ago.
一週前發生的非法藥物買賣事件
-Police! -Don't move!
-我們是警察！ -不准動！
The Kanagawa Prefectural Police
神奈川縣的警察 取得在橫濱的某家酒吧
obtained information on drug deals being made at a bar in Yokohama.
正在進行非法藥物交易的情報後
The police raided a private room in the bar
闖入交易現場的酒吧包廂
and three men were arrested at the scene.
逮捕了三名男性現行犯
One of them was the second son of Akihiko Kawagoe,
得知其中一名嫌犯
The case suddenly became the center of public attention.
此案突然備受關注
But Takumi Kawagoe was the only one of the three men arrested
然而川越拓海是三名被逮的嫌犯當中
who didn't have drugs on him, and denied the accusation.
唯一身上未持有毒品的人 他否認針對自己的指控
He insisted he didn't know anything.
並堅稱自己毫不知情
No, not exactly.
不，我沒那麼認為
It's just that the other suspects admitted to the crime.
不過其他嫌疑犯皆已坦承罪行
His statement has many inconsistencies.
川越的供述不僅有許多矛盾之處
Witnesses saw him frequenting the bar.
也被目擊到頻繁進出案發現場的酒吧
Above all, he was in the small room while the drugs were being sold.
更重要的是嫌犯當時 也坐在狹窄的包廂內進行買賣
You don't have to tell me. I've read what you wrote.
那種事我看資料就知道了 不用你來說明
But you don't have his confession.
可是你沒取得川越本人的供述
He was not in possession of any drugs.
他也沒有攜帶任何毒品
Right.
是的
Either get him to confess…
得設法取得他的供詞…
or collect stronger evidence.
不然就是蒐集更周全的證據
You're not an amateur.
你又不是門外漢
I've heard that Kanade Nishimura is good. But…
雖然我聽說西村奏很能幹…
Is this all you have to show?
原來就這點程度啊？
We needed an indictment in this case at all costs.
無論如何，這起案件一定要起訴
Two years since getting transferred to Yokohama.
自從我調動到橫濱已過了兩年
The city's night sky is too light
都市的夜晚太過明亮
to see any stars.
看不到任何星星
Mr. Nogi.
野木先生
You're not allowed to leave your room without permission.
你又擅自亂跑，這樣不行啦
What are you doing?
你在幹什麼？
Hmm? I was just looking at the stars.
嗯？我只是在看星星
Stars?
星星？
Nurse Hashimoto, when can I leave the hospital?
橋本小姐，我何時才能出院？
-Excuse me? -Um…
-什麼？ -那個…
Hasn't this healed enough?
我的傷已經痊癒了吧？
It's not for me to say.
我不清楚
What did the doctor say?
醫生什麼都沒說嗎？
Nothing.
沒有耶
Should I ask him?
那我幫你問，好嗎？
Yes, thank you.
拜託你了
Confession.
供詞
Evidence.
證據
Evidence…
證據啊…
BAR GLOIRE NAKA-KU, YOKOHAMA
（葛洛瓦爾酒吧 橫濱市中區）
The sight of illegal drug transactions…
毒品的交易現場
I'M KENTA, A REGULAR!
（我是常客的謙太！）
MIZUHARA I FOUND KENTA! I'LL LEAVE A LINK.
（水原：逛部落格發現謙太 貼上我的帳號連結）
EIICHI NAKAMURA
（中村榮一）
NAN-SAN
（阿南）
Huh?
什麼？
Have you been to Bar Gloire before?
你去過葛洛瓦爾酒吧嗎？
It was my first time there.
我是第一次去那裡
-I'm home. -Hi, Takashi.
-我回來了 -回來啦
-Still working? -Mm-hmm.
-還在工作嗎？ -是啊
Don't work too hard.
別太勉強自己
Here. You've got lines right there.
眉間都皺起來了
You know what, Kanade?
我說啊，小奏
Hmm? What?
嗯？什麼事？
Don't you think… it's time we get married?
我們差不多該結婚了吧
He proposed to me as if he were saying "good morning" or "good night."
他用彷彿道早安或晚安的口吻
Good night.
晚安
Get married… huh?
結婚啊
It's been 12 years since Kaori's accident.
香織出意外後過了12年
Masaki disappeared that day,
就在那天，真樹消失了
and I became an empty shell.
我變得宛如一具空殼
Careful!
危險啊…
Where are you going?
你要去哪？
I got a call from a girl.
有女生找我
What?
什麼？
Just kidding. To the store.
騙你的，只是要去超商
I'll be right back.
我馬上回來
You'll be right back…
你明明跟我說…
That's what you said.
會馬上回來
I was alive, but I felt as though I were dead.
那時我過著行屍走肉般的日子
It felt futile no matter how hard I tried.
無論我再怎麼努力都感覺是徒勞無功
What's the matter?
你怎麼了？
Are you okay?
沒事吧？
Yes, I'm okay.
我沒事
-I-I'm sorry. -Take your time.
-不好意思 -慢慢來
I'm sorry.
抱歉
Here.
請喝
It's just hot water, but it will warm you.
只是杯熱開水，不過喝了會暖和些
This is good.
真好喝
It was
那是一杯
magical hot water.
施了魔法的熱開水
He gave me back
他讓我重拾
the will to live.
繼續活下去的精力
Is this seat taken?
我可以坐在這裡嗎？
No.
可以
How are you doing?
你身體狀況如何？
I'm better, thank you.
我很好，都是託你的福
Good.
那就好
Um…
那個…
Thank you so much for your help the other day.
當時真的很感謝你
It's nothing.
不客氣
Careful.
小心
-Are you okay? -I'm sorry.
-沒事吧？ -對不起
I'm sorry.
不好意思
Huh?
什麼？
Hello.
你好
My hospital is over there.
我任職的醫院就在那裡
I-I'm a legal apprentice at Tokyo District Public Prosecutors Office.
我在東京地檢進行司法實習
Oh, so you passed it.
是喔，你通過司法考試了啊？
Yes.
對
-Cheers.
-乾杯
-Congratulations. -Thank you very much.
-真是恭喜你 -謝謝
-That's good. -Ahh.
-真好喝 -天啊
Should I start cooking?
我來烤吧
-Oh, I'll do it. -No, I can do it.
-哦，讓我來 -不，我來就好
Another year went by before we started dating.
自那次重逢的一年後我們開始交往
But being a rookie prosecutor,
不過當時還是個菜鳥檢察官的我
I was transferred outside of Tokyo.
被派到東京以外的縣赴任
And he was too busy at his hospital.
他的工作也忙不過來
Sorry. An emergency patient. I don't think I can make it tonight.
抱歉，突然有急診病患 今天沒辦法赴約
Okay. Good luck with your work.
明白了，加油喔
I'm not free next week. How about the week after?
下週我不方便，約兩週後如何？
I have to go to Fukuoka for a conference that week.
那週我得參加福岡的學會
How about this weekend?
這個週末呢？
A case I'm on is entering the homestretch.
現在正值案件的關鍵收尾，根本沒空
No time to go to Tokyo.
我無法到東京
Dr. Okuda. The preparation for the examination is done.
奧田醫生，已經準備好，可以檢查了
Thank you.
知道了
Is it ever going to work out for us?
我們大概無法在一起了吧
There were times when I almost gave up on dating him.
我曾數次想放棄跟他交往下去
KAEDE, I'LL BE HOME LATE SO NO DINNER TONIGHT
（小奏，我今天會晚歸 不用煮我的晚餐）
He went to work without even hearing my answer to his proposal.
他沒有問我求婚的答覆就去上班了
Was he feeling awkward after all this time?
是因為過一段時間後害羞了嗎？
Or was he just expecting
還是說對他而言
for me to say yes?
我答應求婚是理所當然的事呢？
OUTRAGEOUS SON OF THE SECRETARY-GENERAL OF DLP
（民事黨幹事長的荒唐兒子！）
HIS CIRCLE OF FRIENDS AND DRUG ACQUISITION CHANNELS
（其交友關係與非法藥物入手途徑）
TOMO
（小知）
It's been a while. How are you?
好久不見，過得好嗎？
Kaori's 12th Anniversary Memorial Service is on Sunday. Are you coming?
這個週日有香織 十二週年忌日的法事，你會參加吧？
Yes, I'm planning to.
會，我正有此意
Okay, I'll talk to you then.
那就到時見囉
I know you're busy.
抱歉在百忙之中打擾你
It's fine. I look forward to seeing you.
沒關係，可以久違地見面了呢
However, I had to work on that day after all.
然而我後來還是得工作
The illegal drug dealing case.
之前那起非法藥物案件
This witness interview is the key to the indictment.
我負責詢問該案起訴關鍵的證人
The bar owner where the drug deal took place is the witness.
也就是交易地點的酒吧的店主
BAR GLOIRE OWNER TOSHIKI TAGAWA, AGE 49
（葛洛瓦爾酒吧店主 田川俊樹，49歲）
I'm sorry, but I unexpectedly have a witness interview.
抱歉，我臨時得詢問證人
I might be late.
可能會晚到 結束後馬上就搭新幹線過去！
I see.
明白了
It must be tough working on a Sunday. Best of luck.
星期天還得工作，真是辛苦，加油
That day, Tomo said our friendship might be over.
當年小知說過 “我們之間的友誼可能到此為止了”
But as we got together
不過…
our relationship began to return to what it was.
漸漸回到從前的關係
Mr. Tagawa, the witness, has arrived.
證人的田川先生已經到了
Thank you. I'll be right there.
好，我馬上過去
Sometimes I wonder what it would be like if Tomo had become a prosecutor.
我曾想過如果小知是檢察官的話 會有怎樣的未來
But after she passed the entrance exam for law school,
可是她在考上法科大學後
she simply gave up on the bar exam.
就乾脆地放棄司法考試
The reason was her pregnancy.
原因是懷孕
And the father was…
而且對象是…
Hey, can I wear this today?
你看，我穿這樣行嗎？
No, you have to wear black.
不行啦，得是黑色的
But it's the 12th, and a private event--
-是十二週年忌日，只有自己人… -換成黑色的
Hey, can I wear this today?
你看，我穿這樣行嗎？
Thank you for coming on your day off.
不好意思假日還傳喚你過來
Well…
就是啊
You know, our customers were the ones arrested.
檢察官大人，捅婁子的是店裡的顧客
My bar just got caught up in it.
我們反倒是被牽連的一方
Of course, we understand.
這點我當然知道
We are asking for your cooperation.
還請你務必配合
Mr. Tagawa, when the police questioned you,
田川先生，你在接受警方問話時
you said you didn't know Takumi Kawagoe.
提到與嫌疑犯的川越拓海素昧平生
That's right. I didn't know him.
對，我不認識他
The son of the Secretary-General of the DLP?
聽說他是民事黨幹事長的兒子？
The press is making a big fuss and it's a nuisance to us.
媒體也吵得沸沸揚揚 造成了我很大的困擾
I see.
原來如此
Mr. Tagawa, you must have heard about a bar named La Bilance.
你知道拉比蘭斯這家酒吧，對吧？
Until three years ago,
就在三年前
you owned a bar at the same location under a different name.
你在同樣的場所經營其他店名的酒吧
And the name was La Bilance. Is this correct?
就是拉比蘭斯沒錯吧？
Uh. Yes.
是啊，沒錯
This means the current bar reopened with a different name.
也就是說現在的店是重新開張
Don't you know a man named Eiichi Nakamura?
你認識中村榮一先生吧？
I do. He was a regular at the last bar.
認識，他是上一家店的常客
NAKAMON
（阿中）
EIICHI NAKAMURA
（中村榮一）
This is from Mr. Nakamura's social media.
這是中村先生的社群帳號
If you follow the links back in time,
我回溯他之前的貼文
he was at a party at La Bilance four years ago.
發現四年前在拉比蘭斯的派對上
And you were there too.
你有出席
OWNER AND FRIENDS A PRIVATE FAREWELL PARTY
（店主與他的夥伴 只有自己人參加的離別派對）
Huh?
什麼？
And the person who is next to you in the picture…
照片中在你身旁的人…
POST BY @NAKAMURAXX983
（@nakamuraxx983的貼文）
…is Takumi Kawagoe, the suspect. Is it not?
不就是嫌疑犯的川越拓海嗎？
Have you been to Bar Gloire before?
你去過葛洛瓦爾酒吧嗎？
It was my first time there.
我是第一次去那裡
Why were you hiding this fact from us?
為何你之前一直隱瞞這件事？
Because I…
那是因為…
Mr. Tagawa.
田川先生
You can lie to us all you want.
你要說謊也沒關係
But if you keep this up,
不過照現在這樣下去
we will consider you complicit in the dealing of illegal drugs.
我就當你是默許 在店內進行非法藥物交易
Furthermore, we will have to view you
更具體地來說 你會被視作提供交易場地
as providing the location and assisting in the dealing
協助毒品買賣的幫手
Is that all right with you?
儘管如此，你也無所謂嗎？
No, I…
不，這個嘛…
Kaji, today's deposition should do it, can you prepare the indictment?
加地，憑今天的供述八成能起訴 你先彙整成起訴狀
Yes, ma'am. But do I have to work overtime on my own?
好的，話說只有我得繼續工作嗎？
-I'll buy you lunch. -No need for that.
-我會請你吃午飯 -那倒不必
Can I have a paid day off instead?
可以改成讓我補休嗎？
You're always telling me I can, but it never happens.
你總是嘴上說說 到頭來根本不讓我休假
Kaji, isn't it an assistant officer's job to prepare the indictment?
加地，準備起訴 是事務官的工作對吧？
Uh, yes.
這個嘛，是沒錯
You'll get your day off. I'm counting on you.
我同意你補休，剩下的就拜託你了
-Goodbye.
-辛苦了 -你也是
Thank you both for making time in your busy schedule to come.
真的很感謝兩位在百忙之中來參加
Not at all.
請別介意
Mr. and Mrs. Oikawa, I hope you both stay well.
伯父跟伯母也要多保重
Thank you.
謝謝你
-Take care of yourself, Tomomi. -I will.
-你也要照顧好自己，知美小姐 -好的
If only that accident hadn't happened, Kaori would be like you two by now--
要是沒發生那場意外 香織應該也會跟你們一樣…
Hey.
別說了
I'm sorry.
真是抱歉
I guess it's no use talking about it in this way.
說這種話也於事無補
It's all right.
沒關係
I hope you'll find happiness, for Kaori's sake too.
你們要連同香織的份過得幸福喔
And I hope sometimes
然後啊，也請你們
you'll remember Kaori.
偶爾想起那孩子吧
I've never forgotten her.
我從沒忘過她
Not ever.
一次也沒有
We'll come by to see you again.
我們還會再來的
-Please do. -Thank you.
-好的 -謝謝
Looks like Kanade couldn't make it.
結果小奏還是沒來
There are people you can only interview on weekends, I guess.
因為有些人只有週末才能接受詢問
Having a job is not easy.
有工作的人還真辛苦
Well, it can't be helped.
不過呢，這也沒辦法
"Be happy for Kaori's sake too," she said.
“連同香織的份過得幸福”，是嗎？
-Huh? -I was just wondering.
-怎麼了？ -沒有啦
How can I find happiness for Kaori's sake?
只是在想要怎樣才能 連同香織的份過得幸福
Hey, Mom.
我說啊，媽媽
I know where you want to go. Railway Heritage Park, right?
我知道啦 你想順路去鐵道文化村吧？
Yay! Abt system!
好耶！阿布特式！
Let's go, hurry!
我們快點走吧！
How did he get so simple-minded?
為什麼他會如此單純啊？
Maybe the existence of that kid is our happiness.
或許有那孩子在就是幸福吧
What?
什麼？
Should we get ourselves some soda floats and head home?
我們喝杯冰淇淋汽水後再回家吧
Uhh… Wasn't that a little cheesy?
哦，你難道是在耍帥嗎？
-Why would I be? -Hmm?
-為什麼？幹嘛事到如今那樣？ -什麼？
After that, I visited the university for the first time in a while.
在那之後，我久違地到大學
Although it was Sunday,
雖然是星期天
I saw some students there.
校內卻可見到一些大學生的身影
Similar to how we were back then.
就像當年的我們
That's the seat where Kaori was always drinking melon soda floats.
香織在那個座位上 不知為何總是在喝冰淇淋汽水
-Give me. -Aww.
-我喝一口 -真是的
Hey, don't.
別這樣啦
Tastes terrible.
有夠難喝
-Who cares what you think? I like it. -How can you drink so much of that crap?
-要你管，我就是愛喝 -真虧你能喝這麼多
-Masaki is mine! -What are you talking about?
-真樹是我的！ -你在說什麼啊？
Kanade too! You're mine!
小奏也是屬於我的！
I like both of you!
我最喜歡你們兩個了！
-Ah-ha! -What are you doing?
-啊哈！ -你們在幹什麼？
-Tomo is mine too! -Don't be silly.
-小知也是我的！ -別傻了啦
How about me?
那我呢？
Yuki? I don't think so.
祐希嗎？我才不要
What? That's mean!
啥？那算什麼嘛！
Yuki, come here.
祐希，你來問我
Are you kidding me?
-開什麼玩笑 -那就拜託你了
We were so innocent then.
那時的我們天真無邪
We all liked Kaori.
大家都喜歡香織
She was high-maintenance, audacious,
雖然她的個性麻煩又任性
and childlike.
像個小孩一樣
But we liked her nonetheless.
不過我們都很喜歡她
Then why…
然而為何會…
To the store.
只是要去超商
I'll be right back.
我馬上回來
This accident…
這起意外事故
Do you suppose it was a crime?
有犯罪性嗎？
I wonder if they suspect it wasn't just an accident.
警察可能認為這不是一場單純的意外
What really happened between those two at that time?
當時兩人到底發生了什麼事？
The accident was blamed on Kaori's negligence.
那起以香織的過失結案的事故
Hey! Tell me what happened!
我問你！究竟發生什麼事了？
I'm the one who…
是我把香織…
Masaki…
真樹…
was saying something to me.
在那時對我說了一些話
What did he say?
究竟是什麼？
What was he telling me?
他想告訴我什麼事？
What do you mean he's gone?
你說人不見了是怎麼回事？
As I said, the bed was empty before I realized it.
所以說這名病患 在不知不覺間離開了病床
And I found this.
只留下這個
THANKS FOR THE CARE MEDICAL FEE, NOGI
（感謝你們的照顧，這是診療費 野木）
What's the matter?
怎麼了？
Oh, Dr. Okuda. Well,
哦，奧田醫生，其實啊
a patient brought in as an emergency case left the hospital without permission.
之前被緊急送來的患者 擅自離開病房
Can't you contact him?
目前聯絡不上他嗎？
I'm sorry.
不好意思
Dr. Okuda, the patient's family has arrived.
奧田醫生，病患家屬來了
Yes, thank you.
明白了
MASAKI NOGI, ADMITTED: JULY 11, 2024 PHYSICIAN: DR. KENTARO NAKAMURA
（野木真樹，2024年7月11日住院 主治醫生：中村健太郎）
Wrong room.
走錯了
Sorry, my mistake.
不是這裡，抱歉，我搞錯了
Are you kidding?
開什麼玩笑？
Why?
為什麼？
Why are you here?
為什麼你會在這裡？
Did you know about Kaori's Memorial Service?
你知道今天是香織十二週年的忌日？
Was it you who went to her grave?
去她墓前祭奠的
I wondered how long it had been since I uttered the name Masaki?
“真樹”
Kanade.
小奏
The moment I heard his voice,
在聽到他聲音的瞬間
I was instantly back in those days.
時間一口氣倒轉回當年
I missed you.
我好想你
What's that?
那算什麼？
After all these years…
現在才說？
What are you saying now?
過這麼久了，你是在胡說什麼？
And what were you doing?
待在哪裡？做了什麼？
Masaki.
真樹
Kanade…
小奏
are you a prosecutor now?
你當上檢察官了啊？
Huh?
什麼？
That lapel pin.
我看到了那個徽章
Yes, I've become one.
是啊，我當上了
That's amazing.
真厲害
You kept at it.
你真的很努力呢
Yes.
沒錯
I kept at it.
我的確很努力
I felt like I wanted to die at one point.
之前我曾認真地想尋死
I thought I couldn't believe anyone.
覺得自己再也無法相信任何人
You don't know…
你知不知道我…
how hard it was for me…
我們幾個…
how hard it was for us to get over the death of Kaori.
要克服香織離世的事有多難？
Why did you disappear without telling us?
為何你要默默地消失不見？
Why didn't you say anything?
為什麼要一語不發地失蹤？
How awful of you.
太過分了
So don't you dare tell me now
為什麼現在才說那種話？
that you missed me.
別說什麼很想我
I'm sorry.
抱歉
You're right.
說得也是
Sorry.
對不起
Wait.
別走，等一下
Back then…
在那時候…
what did you say to me?
你究竟對我說了什麼？
On that day when I last saw you.
就是那一天你最後說的話
What went on with you and Kaori?
你跟香織之間發生了什麼事？
Why did Kaori…
為什麼香織會…
Kanade.
小奏
You're amazing.
你很了不起
Seriously.
我是打從心底
I think you're amazing.
這麼覺得
I was relieved the light was turned off.
看到燈沒亮，我鬆了一口氣
I didn't want to face Takashi
我不想懷著這種心情
feeling the way I did.
與貴志見面
Sorry I missed you today. Come visit us when you have more time.
今天沒能見到面，真是遺憾 下次有時間再到我家玩吧
A gathering to remember Kaori.
我們可以一起舉辦香織追思會
Thanks. Sounds great.
謝謝，聽起來很棒
By the way,
其實今天
I saw Masaki today.
我見到真樹了
I ran into him at--
在大學裡偶…
TOMO
（小知）
Hello.
喂？
-What do you mean you saw him? -W-Wait a second.
-什麼意思？怎麼回事？ -等等…
Well, I saw Masaki.
所以說我見到真樹了
-Where? -The university.
-在哪見到？ -大學
I didn't make it to the memorial service, so I visited Kaori's grave.
因為沒趕上法事 我就去香織的墓前祭拜
Then after that, I felt like seeing the university.
之後就想久違地到大學看看
What's that guy doing now?
-那傢伙在幹什麼啊？ -不曉得
Did he know that it was the day of Kaori's service?
他知道這天是香織 十二週年的忌日，所以才出現？
I asked him the same question.
我也跟你說了同樣的話
So, what'd he say?
然後呢？
He said, "Sorry."
他回答說“抱歉”
That's all he said. He disappeared again after that.
就這樣，之後他就不知道上哪去了
Hey Mom. I need my gym clothes for tomorrow.
媽媽，我明天要穿的體育服呢？
What? You're just telling me now? Ask your father.
什麼？怎麼現在才問？去問你爸
-What? -Sorry. I was talking to my son.
-怎麼了？ -抱歉，是我兒子
Anyway, I can't believe it.
他是怎樣？
It's like, "Screw you!" Right?
忍不住會想說“開什麼玩笑！”
Mom. Dad's asleep.
媽媽，爸爸已經睡了
All right. I'll take care of it now.
知道了，我馬上過去，抱歉
Sorry. I'll call you later.
不好意思，我之後再打給你
Hey, you've got to come over soon. Let's talk all about it.
話說你下次來我家吧 我們到時再慢慢談
Yeah. Okay, see you then.
我知道了，好，再見
-Hey, Kanade. -Sorry, what?
-我跟你說，小奏 -抱歉，什麼事？
You'd better not see Masaki.
你不能跟真樹見面喔
You have Takashi now.
現在你身邊已經有貴志先生了
I won't see him.
我才不會見他
I don't have his number--
-我又不知道怎麼聯絡他 -你千萬不能跟他見面喔，答應我
I know.
我知道啦
-Yeah.
-那就好 -嗯
-Bye then. -Okay, bye. Good night.
-再見 -好，再見，晚安
Is something the matter?
發生什麼事了嗎？
Umm, uh, I was just talking with Tomo.
那個，我剛才在跟小知講電話
Sorry if I woke you.
抱歉，吵醒你了吧？
-No. -Oh.
-沒有 -哦
Uh, I wanted to ask you about what I said the other day.
那個，我想問一下
What?
-什麼？ -就是結婚的事
Yeah.
哦
When's your next day off?
你何時能休假？
Well… It'll be after the case I'm on now has been resolved.
我想想，要等現在的案件告一段落後
Let's visit your mother together and tell her about it on your day off.
那到時候我們再一起 去向你母親報告吧
Sounds good.
好啊
Hey.
喂
Whoa. What are you doing over there?
哇，原來你在這裡啊？
I couldn't get to sleep.
不知為何，我睡不著
Kanade said
小奏她說
she ran into Masaki today.
今天見到真樹了
What? No way.
真的假的？不會吧
What could he be thinking after all these years?
他為何現在才突然出現？
Are you listening?
你有在聽嗎？
Yeah. I'm listening.
有啦，當然有在聽
Here.
拿去
Kanade's dad didn't commit suicide.
小奏的爸爸當年不是自殺 是被殺死的
Do you want to die with me?
要不要一起死？
Kanade's dad was--
小奏的爸爸…
Don't say it!
別說了！
So you're saying
你的意思是
you obtained the bar owner's statement to corroborate the crime?
已經從店主口中套出 能證明罪行的供述了，是吧？
Yes.
是的，這樣就能證明 增子與池口的供詞是真的
There is no doubt that Takumi Kawagoe was an accomplice.
果然川越拓海就是共犯，錯不了
Are you sure you can win the case?
你有信心打贏官司嗎？
Yes.
有
I see.
我明白了
Excuse me. Ms. Nishimura.
打擾了，西村檢察官
The witness from the other day says he can't testify in court.
前陣子的證人 表示他不願意在法庭作證
What do you mean?
怎麼回事？
He says he made a mistake.
他說那是他搞錯了
You must be joking.
不可能啊
I kept asking him repeatedly but he suddenly started to play dumb.
我也質問過他好幾次 他卻突然開始裝傻
Hello.
喂？
-Can you explain? -He called just moments ago.
-你能說明一下嗎？ -他剛才打電話告知此事
Oh… I see.
是喔，這樣啊
Yes.
好
So that's what's happening.
原來如此
Understood.
我明白了
Takumi Kawagoe has switched his attorney to Koichiro Nogi.
川越拓海的律師換成野木浩一郎了
This is a tough one.
對方出的招真是棘手啊
It's not rare for the defense counsel to change.
中途更換辯護人並不稀奇
The former prosecutor has come out to squash us, huh?
前檢察官要來擊敗檢方了
How do you feel about the arrest?
關於這次的逮捕你有何看法？
Since the accused is the son of Democratic Liberal Party Secretary-General,
由於嫌疑犯是民事黨 現任幹事長的兒子
they seem to be very eager.
警方似乎在積極調查
However,
不過啊
it was a completely rash move by the police.
這次的逮捕 完全是出自警方的急功近利
Are you saying the arrest itself was a mistake?
意思是警方不該逮捕他嗎？
I think it was an unjust arrest.
這可以說是不當逮捕
I believe the prosecution will not indict under these circumstances.
我相信在這情況下檢方不會起訴
An indictment is impossible.
不可能被起訴
There's just no way.
絕對不可能
So Takumi Kawagoe has no involvement with this case?
川越拓海與案件無關？
Of course not.
那是當然的
That man. It's Masaki's father.
那個人是真樹的父親
Huh?
什麼？
The man on TV
電視上的人就是
was Masaki's father who came to see him after the accident.
在那天的意外發生後趕來的男人 也是真樹的父親
Did Mr. Kawagoe frequent that bar?
川越先生經常光顧那家酒吧？
No comment.
無可奉告
Is the Secretary-General…
請問幹事長…
But that was not all.
但不只是這樣
I had a feeling I had seen a similar scene somewhere before.
對我而言，這好像是似曾相識的場景
The case is a fabrication by the prosecution.
案件是檢方所捏造的
The chief prosecutor forced a confession.
主任檢察官強行逼供
It is outrageous.
太離譜了！
It was a fragment in my memory
是久遠到我快想不起來的
so faint that I couldn't recall it.
記憶片段
-He's here! -There he is!
-他出來了！ -他來了！
In the end, the son of the Secretary-General of the DLP
結果民事黨幹事長川越昭彥的兒子
Takumi Kawagoe was released without indictment
川越拓海因保留處分而被釋放
and the case was later dropped.
之後決定不起訴他
ADDITIONAL RELATED DOCUMENTS
（相關文件補送書）
YOKOHAMA DISTRICT COURT YOKOHAMA SUMMARY COURT
（橫濱地方法院 橫濱簡易法院）
Thank you very much for all your hard work.
這次真的很感謝您
Don't mention it.
您太客氣了
-Goodbye.
-那麼我們告辭了 -再見
I have…
我…
something to ask you.
有事想問你
This is out of the blue.
怎麼這麼突然？
Do you have some time?
能占用一點時間嗎？
All right. Let's go over there.
明白了，到那邊談吧
That patient who ran away the other day?
這是之前逃離病房的那名患者的嗎？
The patient who was brought in with blows to the head and stomach.
他因頭部外傷及 腹部遭重擊被送到醫院
You still haven't been able to contact him?
結果還是聯絡不上他嗎？
No.
是啊，不僅手機打不通
Masaki Nogi…
野木真樹…
Where were you? What have you been doing?
至今為止，你都待在哪裡？ 又做了什麼？
Haven't you thought about how much your family would be worried about you?
你難道沒有想過
-Masaki. -I'm not a kid.
-真樹 -我又不是小孩子
So stop treating me like one.
能不能別用那種語氣跟我說話？
What I wanted to ask you is…
我想問…
about a former Tokyo district prosecutor,
前東京地檢檢察官辻英介的事
Twenty years ago,
二十年前
he committed suicide right before his arrest
他因環境能源貪汙事件
in the environmental energy corruption case.
在快被逮捕前自殺了
I don't know what you're doing now,
我不知道你現在在幹什麼
but did you come to see me just to talk about something like that?
但只是為了那種事才來見我？
You've been missing for over ten years, and now this?
你超過十年杳無音信 結果現在卻是這個樣子？
There's nothing I can tell you.
我對你無話可說
Why are you always like that?
為什麼你總是要這樣？
You always disappoint me.
淨做些讓我失望的事
Are you able to feed yourself?
你能養活自己嗎？
-Are you making a living-- -Don't change the subject.
-為了好好生活… -別轉移話題
All I want
我啊
is to know the truth.
只是想知道真相
I'm in trouble if I don't know it.
不知道的話我會很為難
Is somebody
你…
making you do this?
是不是受人所託？
Don't pry with stupid questions.
別再進行無意義的調查了
Wait.
站住
Kanade's dad didn't commit suicide.
小奏的爸爸當年不是自殺
He was murdered.
是被殺死的
I said wait.
我叫你站住
You shouldn't be seeing Kanade!
真樹不能跟小奏交往！
What the hell is this?
這算什麼啊？
-This is nuts! -Why won't you believe me?!
-你是瘋了嗎？ -為什麼不肯相信我？
What's your problem?
你到底想怎樣？
Let go of me!
給我放開！
Kaori!
香織！
Kanade's dad was--
-小奏的爸爸… -別說了！
Weren't you the one who killed him?
人是你殺的吧？
Did you kill Eisuke Tsuji?
你是不是殺了辻英介？
Say something!
說話啊！
You killed Eisuke Tsuji, didn't you?
是你殺害了辻英介吧？
That's why
所以說
that accident…
才會發生那起事故…
And I…
我…
Kaori was…
我將香織…
The past that I had sealed off
塵封已久的過去
suddenly came rushing back.
突然被喚醒
My father was killed.
殺害我父親
Why do you think your father didn't fight?
你覺得令尊為何不選擇正面迎戰？
What does that have to do with Kaori Oikawa's death?
和及川香織小姐的意外有何關聯？
Sometimes the past needs to be sealed.
有些過去還是封印起來比較好
Marry me.
請跟我結婚
-You'd better not get close to Kanade. -Kanade!
-你別接近小奏 -小奏！
I must not go. I know I shouldn't, but…
雖然我知道自己不該去…